爸爸走了
Look, dad's gone now.
我们得继承他的遗志
We have to carry out his legacy.
能猎杀多少凶鬼恶灵杀多少
Hunting down as many evil sons of bitches as we possibly can.
(忆往昔)
1835年
Back in 1835,
萨穆埃尔·柯尔特为一位猎人造了把枪
Samuel Colt made a gun for a hunter.
这枪能杀任何东西
This gun can kill anything.
只剩四颗子弹了
Only four bullets left.
没有子弹  枪也没用了
Without them, this gun is useless.
它现在唯一的用处
Well, the only thing it's good for now,
就是研究明白它的原理
is figuring out what makes it tick.
枪不错
Cute piece.
打不死恶魔的
Won't stop a demon.
你怎么知道
How the hell would you know?
算是合理推测吧
Call it an educated guess.
你到底要不要我帮你修枪
Do you want me to help you out with that gun or not?
你为救萨姆做的交易
That deal you made to save Sam.
只剩一年了
A year to live.
其实还挺让人觉得解脱的
It's been kind of liberating, actually.
你不怕吗
You're not scared?
当然不
Of course not.
你有多确定
How certain are you
你复活的
that what you brought back...
是百分百纯粹的萨姆
is 100 percent pure Sam?
你觉得我弟弟是不是有毛病
You think something's wrong with my brother?
恶魔都撒谎
Demons lie.
萨姆肯定没事的
I'm sure Sam's okay.
我也这么想
Yeah, me too.
(如今)
(很久很久以前  所有住宅都建得这么好)
你负责转块  我负责木材
You're the brick guy, I'm the wood guy.
一直都是如此
That's the way it's always been.
我就是需要你挑砖块的颜色
I just need someone to pick the color of the bricks.
好吧  埃米特  那只能你来了
Okay. Emmett, you know what, that has gotta be you.
不关我事
Not my responsibility.
那是什么
What was that?
我不知道  狗吗
I don't know. A dog, maybe?
- 狗这么大动静  - 好了
- That's a hell of a dog. - Okay.
早上工人就来了
We got a crew coming in the morning.
看看这木材
Look at this wood, huh?
看啊  烂成什么样
Look at it. It's crap.
你在哪订的
Where'd you order it from?
还是以往那地方
Same place as always.
该按我的意思用煤渣砖的
Should've used the cinder block like I wanted.
又来了
You know what, here we go again.
你不是负责人
You're not in charge.
你们真是群小姑娘
You know, you're a bunch of girls.
关键是这个
Look, it comes down to this, okay?
一股劲风  就能把整栋房子吹倒
One gust of wind and the whole place is gonna blow over.
嗯嗯  随你说吧
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
- 你们听到了吗  - 听到什么
- Did you hear that? - Hear what?
凯尔
Kyle,
来  我们走吧
come on, let's go.
好吧  我先去给卡车热车
Okay, I'm gonna go warm up the truck.
怎么回事
What the hell?
杰克
Jack!
[邪恶力量 第3季第5集]
我不懂  迪恩  为什么不行
I don't understand, Dean. Why not?
因为我说了不行
Because I said so.
- 我们现在有柯尔特枪了  - 萨姆
- We got the Colt now. - Sam.
我们可以召唤十字路口恶魔
We can summon the Crossroads Demon...
- 我们不能召唤什么  - 拿枪指着她
- We're not summoning anything. - Hold the gun on her.
逼她
And force her to
- 解除你的交易  - 我们都不知道
- let you out of the deal. - We don't even know
那能不能行
if that'll work.
那我们就直接打死她
Well then, we'll just shoot her.
如果她死了  交易就解除了
If she dies, the deal goes away.
我们也不知道那能不能行  萨姆
We don't know if that'll work, either, Sam.
你现在跟我说的
All you're pitching me right now,
都是如果  可能  这不够好
is a bunch of ifs and maybes and that's not good enough,
因为如果我们敢钻交易的空子  你会死
because if we screw with this deal, you die.
如果我们不钻空子  你就会死
And if we don't screw with it, you die.
萨姆  够了  我们不想再谈这个了
Sam, enough, I'm not gonna have this conversation.
怎么  因为你说了吗
Why? Because you said so?
对  因为我说了
Yes, because I said so!
你可不是爸爸
Well, you're not Dad.
对  但我是老大
No, but I am the oldest.
我在做最好的选择
And I'm doing what's best.
你就别提这事了  明白了吗
You're gonna let this go, you understand me?
跟我说说那个疯子杀手
Tell me about the psychotic killer.
快点  萨姆  跟我说说那个疯子杀手
Come on, Sam, tell me about the psychotic killer.
疯子杀手
"Psychotic killer:
凶残撕碎被害人
Rips victims apart with brute-like ferocity."
好吧  有提到他的尖牙
Okay, any mention of his razor-sharp teeth,
或利爪  或动物眼吗
or his 4-inch claws, animal eyes?
没有
No.
月相是对的
The lunar cycle's right.
如果是狼人  我们时间不多了
Look, if it is a werewolf, we don't have long.
本周五就是满月了
Moon's full this Friday.
他要过一个月才会再变身
And that's the last time he changes for a month.
两天  不紧张
Two days, no sweat.
我是普兰特警探  这是佩吉警探
I'm Detective Plant, this is Detective Page.
我们是郡警局的
We're with the County Sheriff's Department.
嗯  我一直在等你们
Yeah, uh, been expecting you.
是吗
You have?
等一早上了
All morning.
你们是素描师吧
You are the sketch artist, right?
是的
Absolutely.
- 对  - 是
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我搭档就是素描师
That is exactly who my partner is.
他简直是神笔啊
And the things he can do with a pen.
听着  开始那个之前
But, listen, before we get started on that,
我们想问你
I wanted to ask you...
你怎么逃掉的
how'd you get away?
我不知道
I... I have no idea.
我躲了起来
I was hiding...
他发现了我
and he found me.
他都冲我扑过来了  可又突然停下
He was coming right for me and then he just stopped.
眼神空洞地盯着我
Stared at me with this blank look.
之后  他就跑开了
After that, he just took off running.
好吧
Okay.
我需要你尽量回忆他的身体特征细节
I'm gonna need as much physical detail as you can remember.
好
Yeah.
他大概一米八多
He was about 6 feet tall.
一米八
Six...
黑发
Dark hair.
他的眼睛呢  是什么颜色的
What about his eyes? What color eyes did he have?
可能是蓝色的
Maybe blue?
- 当时很黑  - 蓝色的
- It was dark. - Blue?
他的眼睛看上去像动物吗
Did they seem, uh, ahem, animalish?
什么
Excuse me?
他的牙呢  你注意到什么异常之处了吗
What about his teeth? You notice anything strange about them?
没  就是普通的牙
No, they were just teeth.
牙  好吧
Teeth. Okay.
那他的指甲呢
What about his fingernails?
好吧  他就是个正常人
Okay, look, he's just a normal guy...
有正常的眼睛  牙  和指甲
with normal eyes and teeth and fingernails.
- 先生  没关系...  - 不
- Look, sir, it's okay if... - No.
不
No.
那可是我的兄弟  这人
Those were my brothers. This guy...
他杀了我的兄弟
he killed my brothers.
换你会是什么感觉
How would you feel?
想象不出更可怕的事了
Can't imagine anything worse.
我知道这不容易
I know this isn't easy,
但如果你还能记起什么细节...
but if you could remember any more details...
还有件事  他有个...
There was one more thing. He had a, uh...
卡通人物文身在胳膊上
A tattoo on his arm of a cartoon character.
就是那个...追哔哔鸟的
It's the guy who... He was chasing the Road Runner.
- 大野狼  - 对
- Wile E. Coyote. - Yeah, that's it.
凯尔
Kyle?
加里森医生
Dr. Garrison.
你还好吗
How you holding up?
还算好吧
Okay, considering.
你是凯尔的医生
You're, uh, Kyle's doctor?
是的
Yes.
可以问你几个问题吗
Can I just ask you a few questions?
当然
Sure.
不给我看看吗
Don't I get to see it?
嗯嗯
Yeah, yeah.
只是...半成品
Yeah, it's a, you know, work in progress.
真是...
It's... It's really...
天啊  这真是...艺术品  真的
Boy, this is a piece of, uh, art. Really.
得了  难道你能画得更好吗
Yeah, like you could've done it better.
医生是怎么说凯尔的兄弟的
So what did the doc have to say about Kyle's brothers?
说得不多  他们在现场就死了
Not much. They were DOA at the scene.
但他给我讲了验尸报告
He did give me the lowdown on the coroner's report.
我猜猜  他们的心不见了
Let me guess, their hearts were missing.
并没有
Nope.
但他们肾脏  肺和肠子都缺了大块
But chunks of their kidneys, lungs and intestines.
恶心
That's just gross.
是啊  而且也绝不是狼人的行为
Yeah, also definitely not werewolf behavior.
那怎么  是恶魔吗
So, what, a demon?
袭击者可能被附身了
Attacker could've been possessed.
恶魔怎么会袭击人时突然停下
Why would a demon stop halfway through an attack?
我觉得...
I think that...
可能...
Could it...?
- 嗯  我想不到  - 我也是
- Yeah. I got nothing. - Me neither.
好吧  我饿死了
Okay, I am starving.
等等  能量棒都哪去了
Wait, where are all the PowerBars?
你都吃了
You ate them all
我们还迷路了
and we're lost.
我们没迷路  小路就在这里
We're not lost. The path is right here.
看
Look,
那里
there.
文明啊
Civilization.
嗯
Yeah.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
你俩还好吗
Are you two doing okay?
- 其实  我们...  - 迷路了
- Actually, we're... - Lost.
这难免的  小路弯弯曲曲
It happens. The trail gets twisty...
而且这里就我一户人家
and my house is the only one left up here.
我可以给你们指路
I could point you in the right direction...
但恐怕你们要走好一阵才能回去
but I'm afraid it'll take a while to get back.
你们真的在森林深处了
You're really deep into the woods.
好样的  肯
Nice work, Ken.
你们要进来休息一下吗
Would you like to come in and rest a bit?
好啊
Yeah.
谢谢  但我们还是回去吧
Thanks, but we should head back.
来吧  亲爱的  她都邀请我们了
Come on, honey, she offered.
她就是个无害的老太太  还能怎么样啊
She's a harmless old lady. What could happen?
你确定你不想再来点了吗
You sure you don't want more?
不了  谢谢
No, thank you. It's...
我饱了
I'm full.
我们该走了
We should go.
我们真对你感激不尽
We really can't thank you enough.
肯
Ken?
你...
You...
怎么回事
What's going on?
- 你...  - 我们...
- You...? - Are we...?
你给我们下药了吗
Did you drug us?
朱莉  快跑
Julie, run.
停下
Stop.
求你  快停下
Please, you have to stop.
别担心
Don't worry.
一切都会没事的
Everything's fine.
你别动就好  亲爱的
You just hold still now, dear.
停下
Stop!
停下  求你
Stop, please stop!
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
不
No!
(急诊)
拜托
Please. Please.
我们需要观察你的情况
We need to observe you.
好吗  你体内可能还有药物
All right. The drugs still may be in your system.
我得走了  我还有事要做
I have to go. I have things to do.
- 我得去做安排  - 那不急
- Arrangements I need to make. - It can wait.
你需要休息
Now you need to rest.
留下吧
Stay.
我就回来
Be back in a few minutes.
警探
Detectives.
加里森医生
Dr. Garrison.
这到底怎么回事
What the hell's going on here?
我的小镇都发疯了
My whole town's going insane.
我们查明白了马上告诉你
We'll let you know as soon as we do.
沃森女士
Ms. Watson?
我们需要问你几个问题
We just need to ask you a few questions.
我们还得再说一遍吗
Do we have to go over this again?
非得现在说吗
Now?
我们会尽量不占用你太多时间
We'll try to be brief.
沃森女士  能告诉我们你怎么逃走的吗
Ms. Watson, can you tell us how you got away?
我没像肯吃的那么多
I didn't eat as much as Ken did
所以我还算清醒
so I wasn't as out of it.
那老妇人
And when the old woman was...
砍杀肯时
carving up Ken...
我推了她
I shoved her
她摔倒了
and she fell.
脑袋磕碎在了炉子上
Cracked her head on the stove.
她死了  是吧
She's dead, right?
我...杀了她
I...? I killed her?
你知道她为什么要这么对你吗
Do you have any idea why she did this to you?
不知道
No.
前一刻
One minute...
她还是个好心老太太
she's just a sweet old lady...
转眼间  她就变成了怪物
and the next, she was like a monster.
你还记得别的吗
Can you remember anything else?
嗯
Yeah.
你们找到现场的那个小女孩了吗
Did you find a little girl there by any chance?
小女孩吗
A little girl?
在房子那里吗
At the house?
我好像看到她在窗外
I thought I saw her outside the window.
她...就不见了
She... She just disappeared.
凭空消失了
Just vanished into thin air.
肯定是药的关系吧
It must've been the drugs.
这个消失的女孩  她什么样
This disappearing girl what did she look like?
这重要吗
Does it matter?
是的  一切细节都很重要
Yes, every detail matters.
她有深色的头发
She had this dark, dark hair...
苍白的皮肤
and really pale skin.
她大概八岁
She was around 8.
她是个很美的孩子
She was a beautiful child. It was...
在那样可怕的情况下看到她好奇怪
odd to see her in the middle of something so horrible.
到处都没看到有硫磺  电磁场怎么样
Well, there's no sulfur anywhere. How about the EMF?
嗯  爆表了
Yeah, it's going nuts.
但只在窗边有
But only over here by the window.
这里绝对来过鬼魂
There was definitely a spirit here.
还站在犯罪现场外面看
Who stood outside the crime scene and watched.
看来是的
Looks like.
你怎么想
What the hell do you make of that?
其实  我有个理论
Actually, I do have a theory.
算是有吧
Sort of.
说吧
Hit me.
我在想童话
Well, thinking about fairy tales.
好可爱啊
That's... That's nice.
你经常想童话吗
You think about fairy tales often?
不  迪恩  我是说这些凶案
No, Dean, I'm talking about the murders.
一男一女  在林子里徒步
A guy and girl hiking through the woods...
差点被个老太太吃了
an old lady tries to eat them.
那是《糖果屋》
That's Hansel and Gretel.
然后还有三兄弟
Then we got the three brothers
为怎么建房吵了起来
arguing over how to build houses...
随后遭到恶狼袭击
attacked by the big bad wolf.
- 《三只小猪》  - 嗯
- Three Little Pigs. - Yeah.
那三个家伙还真是挺胖的
Actually, those guys were a little chubby.
等等  那些故事的结局
Wait. I thought those things ended with
不都是大家幸福地生活了下去吗
everybody living happily ever after.
不  原版可不是
No, no, not the originals.
格林兄弟的故事
See, the Grimm brothers' stuff
其实是当时的民间传说
was kind of like the folklore of its day...
充满了性  暴力和食人
full of sex, violence, cannibalism.
但故事随时间演变得和谐多了
Then it got sanitized over the years...
最终成了迪士尼电影和睡前故事
turned into Disney flicks and bedtime stories.
所以你觉得凶案是故事重演吗
So you think the murders are, uh, what, a reenactment?
有点疯狂吧
That's a little crazy.
像什么一样疯狂
Crazy as what?
我们每天的生活吗
Every day of our lives?
说得好
Touche.
那个瘆人的鬼姑娘怎么说
How's the creepy ghost girl involved?
她出现肯定是有原因的
Well, she must've been here for a reason.
我敢打赌
I'm willing to bet you top dollar
她之前还出现在了建筑工地
she was at the construction site too.
我们现在得去做调研了  是吧
We gotta do research now, don't we?
(坎伯兰郡中央图书馆)
- 怎么样  - 查遍了他们的记录
- So? - Checked every record they had.
儿童暴力死亡案件数
Found the usual amount of
就这么大的小镇而言算是正常量
violent childhood deaths for a town this size.
好
Okay.
知道其中多少涉及黑头发
You wanna know how many were little girls,
苍白皮肤的小女孩吗
with black hair and pale skin?
- 零  - 零
- Zero. - Zero.
知道有多少黑头发
You wanna know how many little girls
苍白皮肤的小女孩失踪了吗
with black hair and pale skin have gone missing?
又答对了  零  无  没有
Right again: Zip, zilch, nada.
拜托告诉我你有所发现
Tell me you got something good
因为我完全浪费了六个小时
because I've totally wasted the last six hours.
你听说过莉莉安·贝利吗
Well, you ever hear of Lillian Bailey?
是1930年代的一个英国灵媒
She was a British medium from the 1930s.
她喜欢童话吗
She got a thing for fairy tales?
不是  是出神
No, trances.
她会进入不省人事的状态  听好
See, she'd go into these unconscious states where, get this,
而她的思维和行为都会完全被鬼魂控制
her thoughts and actions were completely controlled by spirits.
鬼傀儡师
The ghost Puppet Master.
对
Yeah.
你觉得这孩子就在这么做吗
Think that's what this kid is doing?
让大灰狼和老太婆进入出神状态
Sending Wolfboy and Grandma into trances,
让他们疯狂杀戮
making them go kill-crazy?
可能吧
It could be.
就像鬼魂催眠
You know, kind of like a spirit hypnosis or something.
出神我理解  但童话出神
Trances I get, but fairy-tale trances?
即便对于我们也够怪的
That's bizarre even for us.
你说得对  这真是正常呢
Yeah, you're right. That's completely normal.
好吧  或许真是童话
All right, maybe it is fairy tales.
非常糟糕的童话
Totally messed-up fairy tales.
告诉你  我绝不亲青蛙
I tell you one thing, there's no way I'm kissing a damn frog.
看啊
Check that out.
怎么了  万圣节要到了
Yeah? It's close to Halloween.
记得《灰姑娘》吗
You remember Cinderella?
变成马车的南瓜
With the pumpkin that turns into a coach
和变成马的老鼠
and the mice that become horses?
哥们  你还能更基点吗
Dude, could you be more gay?
别回答
Don't answer that.
谁知道呢  或许你能找到你的仙女教母
Well, who knows? Maybe you'll find your fairy godmother.
救命  我在这里
Help, I'm in here.
别担心  没事  我们来了  我们会救你的
Don't worry, it's okay. We're here. We got you.
帮帮我  她疯了
You have to help me. She's a lunatic.
怎么回事
What happened?
我继母  她发狂了  冲我大吼
My stepmom, she just freaked out, screamed at me,
打我  还把我铐了起来
beat me, chained me up.
- 她人呢  - 我不知道
- Where is she now? - I don't know.
萨姆
Sam?
你是谁
Who are you?
医务人员接走了灰姑娘
Paramedics picked up Cinderella.
- 好啊  - 嗯
- That's good. - Yeah.
小女孩  大红苹果
So little girl, shiny red apple.
你应该明白这意味着什么吧  童话小子
I'm guessing that means something to you, fairy tale boy.
我觉得是《白雪公主》
I think it's Snow White.
《白雪公主》
Snow White?
我看过那部电影
I saw that movie.
至少看过色情片版的
Well, the porn version anyways.
有个邪恶继母
There was this wicked stepmother.
她还真是邪啊
She was wicked.
的确有个邪恶继母
There is a wicked stepmother...
她企图用毒苹果害死白雪公主
and she tries to kill Snow White with a poisoned apple.
但苹果并没害死那姑娘  是吧
But the apple doesn't actually kill the girl, right?
对
No.
让她陷入深眠
Puts her into a deep sleep.
就像个活死人
So deep, it's almost like she's dead.
没有  抱歉  我们没有陷入昏迷的小女孩
No, sorry. We don't have any comatose little girls.
- 你确定吗  - 是的
- Are you sure? - Totally.
昏迷病人大都是老人
It's mostly old guys.
还有卡莉
And, well, Callie.
她在我来之前就入院了
She's been around since before I started here.
卡莉
Callie?
对  太悲惨了
Yeah, it's so sad.
可怜的加里森医生  他不肯放弃她
And poor Dr. Garrison, he just won't give up on her.
卡莉是他的病人吗
Was Callie one of his patients?
不  是他女儿
No, his daughter.
(格林兄弟)
这里呢
Here we are.
"按下门栓就行"  外婆喊道
"'Just press the latch,' called out the grandmother."
"我太虚弱了  无法起身"
'I'm too weak to get up.'
大恶狼按下门栓  门开了
The wolf pressed the latch and the door opened.
他走进去  直扑向了外婆
He stepped inside, went straight to the grandmother...
吃了她
"...and ate her up. "
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
(卡·加里森)
猎人走进去
"The huntsman stepped inside
床上躺着大恶狼
and in the bed lay the wolf."
于是猎人拿起剪刀
So the huntsman took a pair of scissors...
切开了大恶狼的肚皮
"And cut open the wolf's belly."
警探  有什么事吗
Detectives, can I help you?
我们刚听说卡莉是你女儿
We just heard that Callie is your daughter.
我们想说一声我们很为您遗憾
And we wanted to say how very sorry we are.
谢谢了
Well, um, thank you.
失陪一下
If you'll excuse me.
我们正要往这边走  我们陪你吧
We're heading this way, we'll walk with you.
卡莉昏迷这样多久了
How long has Callie been like that?
我们无意打探
We don't mean to intrude.
我们无法想象
We can't possibly understand
你看到她这副样子心里会多难过
how hard it must be for you seeing her like this.
是啊  是不容易
Yeah, it's not easy.
她从八岁起就陷入了昏迷
She's, uh, been here since she was 8 years old.
她是那时中毒的吗
That's when she was poisoned?
对  吞了漂白剂
Yes, swallowed bleach.
一直不知道她怎么会拿到那东西
Never figure out how she got her hands on the bottle.
是我妻子发现了她  带她来了急诊室
My wife found her, brought her to the ER.
我当时正好当班
Here, and I was on call.
你妻子...
Your wife was, uh...?
是卡莉的继母吗
Was that Callie's stepmother?
是的  你怎么知道的
Actually, yes. How'd you know that?
猜的
Lucky guess.
朱莉是卡莉唯一知道的母亲
Well, Julie was the only mother that, uh, Callie ever knew.
我妻子去年过世了
My wife passed away last year and...
现在只剩我和我女儿了
it's just my daughter and me now.
我只剩她了
She's all I got left.
X光技术员  分机2407
X-ray tech, extension 2407.
- 失陪  我得回去工作了  - 嗯
- Excuse me, I've gotta get back to work. - Yeah.
你说对了  妥妥的白雪公主
Well, you're right. It's Snow White in spades.
是啊  继母毒害女孩  害她陷入深眠
Yup. Stepmom poisons the girl, puts her into a deep sleep.
你说是什么动机
What's the motive, you think?
可能是像米莎·巴顿那样
Could be like Mischa Barton.
《灵异第六感》不是《橘子郡男孩》
Sixth Sense, not The O. C.
什么
What?
你了解童话  我了解电影
You know fairy tales, I know movies.
她演了那个苍白的鬼
She played the pasty ghost.
就她妈妈有那个毛病
You know, remember the mom had that thing, you know...
让孩子生病  好博关注
where you keep the kid sick so you get the attention?
嗯嗯
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
代理型孟乔森综合征
Munchausen syndrome by proxy.
有可能
Could be.
或许那么多年来  卡莉一直默默承受着
So say all these years, Callie's been suffering silently...
因为没人知道亲爱的老妈做了什么
because nobody knows the truth about what Mommy Dearest did.
过了这么久
And after all this time,
她的鬼魂越来越愤怒
her spirit just gets angrier and angrier,
直到终于开始发脾气
until it finally just starts lashing out.
而与此同时  她还一直听着老爸
Meanwhile, she has to listen to Dad
给她讲各种疯狂的故事
tell her these deranged stories...
什么疯狼  食人老妇
about a rabid wolf or a cannibalistic old lady.
这足以把任何人逼疯了
It's enough to drive anybody nuts.
好吧  但我们怎么阻止她
Okay, but how are we gonna stop her?
卡莉困在这里了  她父亲在用机器维系她的生命
I mean, Callie's stuck here. Her father's keeping her body alive.
这样想烧她尸骨的确有难度
It does make it a bit hard to burn the bones.
还用说
You think?
进来了
Coming in.
你把好了吗
You got it?
她情况如何
What's her status?
72岁老妇
Seventy-two-year-old female.
多处撕裂伤和穿刺伤
Sustained multiple lacerations and puncture wounds.
血压80/40  还在降低  窦性心搏过速
BP is 80/40 and falling. Sinus tachycardia.
那是咬伤吗
Is that a bite?
她似乎是被疯狗或狼咬了
It looks like she was mauled by a mad dog or maybe a wolf.
加里森医生给卡莉读的最后的故事是什么
What was the last story Dr. Garrison was reading Callie?
《小红帽》
Little Red Riding Hood.
不好意思
Excuse me.
她是唯一的受害人吗
Was she the only victim?
她被发现时躺在路边  奄奄一息
She was found by the side of the road, barely alive.
独自一人
Alone.
我们需要找到她的亲属
We need to find her next of kin.
嗯  她有个外孙女
Yeah. She has a granddaughter.
有地址吗
Do you have an address?
谢谢
Thank you.
Thanks.
你想办法阻止卡莉
You find a way to stop Callie, all right?
你呢
What about you?
我要去阻止大恶狼
I'm gonna go stop the big bad wolf.
这是我说过的最奇怪的话了
Which is the weirdest thing I've ever said.
外婆
Grandma.
加里森医生  我需要跟你谈谈
Dr. Garrison, I need to speak with you.
警探  有什么事吗
Detective, what can I do for you?
嗯...
Well...
是关于卡莉的
It's about Callie.
我女儿  她怎么了
My daughter? What about her?
或许...我们可以坐下谈谈
You know, maybe, maybe, could we sit down for a minute?
不行  她怎么了
No. What about her?
好吧
Okay, well...
医生  这会让你很不好受
All right, doctor, this isn't gonna be easy.
卡莉的事不是意外
What happened to Callie was not an accident.
什么
Excuse me?
很抱歉  但这是真的
I'm sorry but it's true.
你才不知道我女儿遭遇了什么
You have no idea what happened to my daughter.
有些事你不知道  医生
There are things you don't know, doctor...
关于你妻子的事
about your wife.
我妻子
My wife?
医生  是你妻子给卡莉下了毒
Doctor, your wife poisoned Callie.
你为什么要对我说这种可怕的话
Why would you say something so horrible to me?
因为我需要你帮忙
Because I need your help.
你远离我和我女儿  听到了吗
You stay away from me and from my daughter, you understand?
医生  这不是...
Doctor, this isn't...
拜托...
Please, if...
我要叫保安了
I'm calling security.
不  听着
No, listen,
我没时间跟你好声好气了
I don't have time to do this gently.
如果你不听我的  会有更多人受伤
If you don't listen to me, more people are gonna get hurt.
因为卡莉要伤害他们
Because Callie is going to hurt them.
你说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
你会觉得我疯了  但请听我说
You're gonna think I'm crazy, but just understand me.
你女儿卡莉  她还在
Your daughter, Callie, is still here.
她是个鬼魂
She's a spirit.
所以你也看到她了
So you've seen her too?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
嗯
Yeah...
我能感觉到她
I sensed her.
卡莉
Callie.
她的存在  她的气息
Her presence, her scent.
我甚至看到她站在我床脚  但我从未...
I even saw her standing at the foot of my bed, but I never...
相信过  我以为那是做梦
believed it. I thought I was dreaming...
那不是做梦
It wasn't a dream.
她看上去还是八岁时的样子
She looks like she did when she was 8.
白裙子
White dress.
头发上有红缎带
Red ribbon in her hair.
她一直想对你说话
She's been trying to talk to you.
你不是警察  是吧
You're not a cop, are you?
不是
No.
那你是什么人
Then who are you?
我是对这种事有所了解的人
Someone who knows a little bit about this kind of thing.
但你说我妻子给卡莉下了毒...
But what you said about my wife poisoning Callie, that...
先生  是卡莉告诉我们的
Sir, Callie told us.
- 什么  - 并非是用语言
- What? - Not in so many words.
但是以她自己的方式
But in her own way...
她告诉我们了
she told us.
我妻子爱卡莉  那怎么可能
My wife loved Callie. So how is that possible?
我不知道  但就是如此
I don't know, but it is.
不  我不信
No. No, I don't believe you.
卡莉在杀人
Look, Callie is killing people.
她很愤怒  很绝望
She's angry, she's desperate...
因为没人肯听她的
because nobody will listen to her.
所以你必须聆听她
So you have to listen to her.
拜托了
Please...
好好聆听你女儿吧
listen to your daughter.
卡莉
Callie?
卡莉  是爸爸
Callie, it's Daddy.
是我  爸爸
It's me, Daddy.
是真的吗
Is it true?
是妈妈害了你吗
Did Mommy do that to you?
我知道我之前没好好听  但我现在听了
I know I wasn't listening before, but I'm listening now.
爸爸在呢
Daddy's here.
拜托  亲爱的  你能告诉我吗
Please, honey. Is there any way you can tell me?
医生
Doctor.
是真的吗
Is it true?
真对不起  宝贝
I'm so sorry, baby.
但听我说
But listen to me.
你必须停下你在做的事  好吗
You gotta stop what you're doing, okay?
你在伤害人
You're hurting people.
我现在什么都知道了
I know everything now.
我知道真相了
I know the truth.
你该放手了
It's time for you to let go.
我该对你放手了
It's time for me to let you go.
停下
Stop, stop.
Stop.
我在哪
Where am I?
这怎么回事
What's going on?
X光技术员  分机...
X-ray tech, extension...
那姑娘没事吧
And the girl's okay?
那真的结束了
So it's really over.
嗯
Yeah.
多亏了你
All thanks to you.
卡莉曾是我生命中最重要的部分
Callie was the most important thing in my life...
但我早该对她放手了
but I should've let her go a long time ago.
回见了  医生
See you around, doc.
希望不会再见了
I sure hope not.
他说的话
You know what he said?
是好建议
Some good advice.
你希望我那么做吗  迪恩
Is that what you want me to do, Dean?
对你放手
Just let you go?
哎呦  小萨姆·温彻斯特
Well, little Sammy Winchester.
我真感动
I'm touched.
你哥哥来见过我两次了  但你...
I mean, your brother's been to see me twice, but you...
我还未曾有幸
I never had the pleasure.
我能为你做什么  萨姆
What can I do for you, Sam?
你可以求饶
You can beg for your life.
我们本来聊得好好的呢
We were having such a nice conversation.
你非要破坏气氛
Then you had to go and ruin the mood.
如果我是你  就不再耍嘴皮  开始害怕
If I were you, I'd drop the wisecracks and start acting scared.
那不是我的风格
It's not my style.
那不是原本的柯尔特枪
That's not the original Colt.
你从哪弄到的
Where did you get that?
露比
Ruby.
肯定是
Had to be.
她真是个麻烦精
She is such a pain in my ass.
她会有应得的下场的
She'll get what's coming to her.
- 你等着瞧吧  - 够了
- You can count on it. - That's enough.
我来是有个提议给你
I came here to make you an offer.
你有提议给我吗
You're gonna make me an offer?
真可爱
That's adorable.
你马上解除迪恩的交易
You can let Dean out of his deal right now.
他活  我活  你也活
He lives, I live, you live.
大家皆大欢喜
Everyone goes home happy.
否则
Or...
你永远停止呼吸
you stop breathing. Permanently.
这么强硬
All this tough talk.
我得告诉你  不怎么让人信服
I have to tell you, it's not very convincing.
拜托  萨姆
I mean, come on, Sam.
你真想破坏交易吗
Do you even wanna break the deal?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我不知道
I don't know.
你还没受够给迪恩收拾烂摊子吗
Aren't you tired of cleaning up Dean's messes?
或是应付他破碎的心
Of dealing with that broken psyche of his?
你还没受够被他呼来喝去
Aren't you tired of being bossed around
像个乳臭未干的小弟弟
like a snot-nosed little brother?
你比迪恩强大  你比他好
You're stronger than Dean, you're better than him.
说话小心点
Watch your mouth.
承认吧
Admit it.
你只是来走个过场
You're here, going through the motions.
其实  等他不在了  你会有那么一丝解脱
The truth is you'll be a tiny bit relieved when he's gone.
闭嘴
Shut up.
摆脱了绝望  大意  粘人的迪恩
No more desperate, sloppy, needy Dean.
你终于能自由了
You can finally be free.
我说了  闭嘴
I said, shut up.
要我说  你反驳得太激烈了
Doth protest too much if you ask me.
好了  我受够你的胡扯了
All right, I've had enough of your crap.
你马上解除迪恩的交易
You let Dean out of his deal right now.
抱歉  亲爱的  但你哥哥是成年人了
Sorry, sweetheart, but your brother's an adult.
他自愿做了那个交易  公平公正
He made that deal of his own free will. Fair and square.
牢不可破
It's ironclad.
每个交易都可以打破
Every deal can be broken.
这个不能
Not this one.
好啊  那我杀了你
Fine, then I'll kill you.
如果你不在了  交易也就不在了
If you're gone, so is the deal.
猜错了
Guess again.
什么
What?
萨姆  我只是推销的
Sam, I'm just a saleswoman.
我也像其他人一样有老板
I got a boss like everybody.
合同在他手里  不在我手里
He holds the contract, not me.
他很想要迪恩的灵魂
He wants Dean's soul, bad.
相信我  他不会放手的
And believe me, he's not gonna let it go.
你在唬人
You're bluffing.
是吗
Am I?
打死我吧  如果能让你爽一把
Shoot me, if it'll get you off.
但交易不会被打破
But the deal still holds.
等迪恩大限到了  他会被拖入深渊
And when Dean's time is up, he's getting dragged into the pit.
那你的老板是谁
Then who's your boss?
合同在谁手里
Who holds the contract?
我告诉你  他可不像我这么温柔
He's not as cuddly as me, I can tell you that.
他是谁
Who is it?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
抱歉  萨姆
I'm sorry, Sam...
这事没有出路
but there's no way out of this one.
这次没有
Not this time.